{
    "subject": "resource/Hairspray_(2007_film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Films_about_interracial_romance",
    "human_readable": "The subject of the film Hairspray (2007) is about interracial romance.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9166874885559082,
            "question": "How realistic is the portrayal of interracial relationships in Hairspray (2007)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.880040168762207,
            "question": "Does Hairspray (2007) contribute to positive social change regarding interracial relationships?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8715847730636597,
            "question": "Is interracial love a central plot point in Hairspray (2007)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8358510136604309,
            "question": "What type of romance is depicted in the film Hairspray (2007)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7015889883041382,
            "question": "What is the main theme of the film Hairspray (2007)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6549474000930786,
            "question": "Does Hairspray (2007) promote understanding between different racial groups?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6515078544616699,
            "question": "How does Hairspray (2007) address issues of racial prejudice?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5918856859207153,
            "question": "Does Hairspray (2007) explore a relationship between people of different races?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4961254298686981,
            "question": "What are some challenges faced by characters in a relationship due to their different races in Hairspray (2007)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3580341637134552,
            "question": "What message about acceptance and tolerance does Hairspray (2007) convey?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of the film Hairspray (2007) is about interracial romance.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6124_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some challenges faced by characters in a relationship due to their different races in Hairspray (2007)?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6124_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Hairspray (2007) explore a relationship between people of different races?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6124_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does Hairspray (2007) address issues of racial prejudice?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6124_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6124_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6124_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6124_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6124_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6124_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6124_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6124_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6124_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6124_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6124_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents mention that the film Hairspray (2007) deals with issues of racial segregation and fat-shaming, but most notably it mentions the romantic relationship between Tracy and Link as being based on personality rather than physical attractiveness. However, they also highlight the issue of interracial romance in general through the subplot involving Penny and her black boyfriend. Additionally, one of the documents mentions that Hairspray's portrayal of history may lack depth to the time it is set, but it does depict the backdrop of a white musical love story amidst the Civil Rights Movement.\n\nThe correct interpretation would be that while Hairspray (2007) primarily focuses on the theme of Tracy's self-love journey and being an intersectional masterpiece with regards to its portrayal of non-conventionally attractive female characters in relationships, it does touch upon and highlight the theme of interracial romance through the subplot involving Penny."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that the subject of the film Hairspray (2007) includes themes related to interracial romance, as evidenced by phrases like \"her mother becomes furious\" when Penny falls in love with a black boy and \"the interracial love really shows how harsh it was for interracial couples during this time period.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}